Hello, welcome to the next episode of Learn German in Hindi.
Today we are going to
learn my favorite concept, the White
Tiger Connect. Right now, why is this my favorite
concept? The easier it is, the more important it is. It is
very easy, isn't it? Today we are going to
organize some sentences and do
something. It is important because
after using them, your language starts to
look next level because we are
also at one level. So, as much as grammar is
important, showing that
we can speak at a slightly higher level in our language is
also important. So, for
example, look, in Hindi, I drink tea and
coffee. It sounds normal. I not
only drink tea but coffee also sounds
very high level. In English,
if you drink high quality coffee, it sounds very high
quality, but also coffee
sounds very next level. So, just like this, we are going to learn to make
complex sentences from very simple connectors
to high level sentences. So,
this is the White Helicopter. So,
friends, this sentence is added near the sentence
and that simple five is  We are going to learn that work.
First I will give you just
a list of 15 and then we are going to learn each one in
detail. So first see which one
is Nishan order now can not only but also
in English. Second is Twitter current affair
and third is the turnoff opposite to that, he does not
sleep here. This is a little now its interface is
all two but the fifth one is - joint inside set on
one side, that on the other side and one hand inside. So
now using these five we
learn to make national sentences like this. So first of all the
simplest Nishan and Jordan will come, that
means not only but also this I had said
that I not only want but I also copied it
but you have to say this, what will you say in English, I don't
drink not only the
angry birds office what will happen in German
sprinkle misnomer tags on the rock play
soil is nothing simple sentence
structure semi keep this green superintendent and
tagged unique twist similarly if the not only
cricket button softball is pillar in amlo
a cricket jounder out Pushpa very
simple  On the side, if you want to do more here, then
what will you do and Twitter order in
Twitter user login Idoltree and copy Mayat I
drink tea, so what will happen,
Spring Kayna in German, Twitter The Amazing
clothes,
a simple but only your tractor, if you
see, then I play, when cricket
and football is pillar and veteran cricket
order, at that time here simple, its holder glance
and in English here waiter knock, I don't
drink Niger t9 coffee is trick where tagged
knock on that
I plane there cricket and football
spillway, this cricket Noakhali very simple, I have
not changed anything in the name in a sentence, we have only taught six words,
cursed from inside for proper and
minutes, from the side it is simple, but in it the
root of the platform is like the one which is
riding and from inside it has sex, the
lesson of that sentence is formed which I last
saw, then on the question, do this, then
we see, then this is I like
team, divide print copy alive typing coffee,
we will do this a little  You can speak with emotion,
oil, two it watering copies,
so this which can make Om in the garden, you can
wish
that after springing on you,
mother after a lot of product, why did the four become part of the first sentence,
that is why pharmacists apply this trick on you, Kavya
your ocular, we have first
Sikander temple operation, it does not do some sentences, it is
clear, similarly all so I
like cricket, but you left hair grooming massage
cricket our love loot hair, it will be very simple
and the last consumption was
accepted in the update not to use much, on one side
this is, on the other side there is one hand inside,
but to complete the concept we also learn that
and one hand and this decision and good are
inside, details are obscene, on one hand
Tesla is good, but on the other hand it is expensive, so
how can it be or it will not go because it will
come in the second position, Tesla is
very simple on the chat start in the group, you will not have to do anything, I will
not say money, so it is most
important, see if you see, the first
three are very simple, you are your normal  You
can use it in sentences, if there
is an interviewer version instead, then we have a concept,
so don't use it wherever you see it, that is,
if one foot you do this in 2019, do
n't do it like I drink tea and coffee, now I
always drink not only tea leaves also, if there is a
need there then subscribe, you
say not only tea and coffee also drink, so in this
way all
quiet active watering coffee and
understand the emotion in it, don't sleep, yes the concept is
very easy, if you see, what did we
see today, only 10 words after seeing 5
and only the door inside the side inside the
platform saw that they
become part of the sentence and we have come to make such complex
sentences, so the window of how to do this is very
simple, but as I said, it should
not be used everywhere, yes, it has to be used wherever it is needed,
set this a
very-very important and very very easy
concept, I hope you all
liked this concept, we will meet
in the next episode, thank you